Guide to the Winston Weisman Collection of Architectural Photographs [1950]-1973 depicting structures ca. 1850 - 1970 PR 73
© 2011 New-York Historical Society
- Series I. Mounted Copy Prints 1850 -- 1970
  - MANHATTAN, NEW YORK (by street address)
    - 27 -- 36 West 23rd Street (Box 25, Folder 474)
      includes Stern Bros. Dry Goods Building
    - 45 -- 47 West 23rd Street (Box 25, Folder 475)
    - 66 -- 68 West 23rd Street (Box 25, Folder 476)
      McCreery's Building
    - 222 West 23rd Street (Box 25, Folder 477)
      The Chelsea Hotel
    - 32 East 26th Street (Box 25, Folder 478)
      Union League Club
    - West 33rd Street and Ninth Avenue (Box 25, Folder 479)
      New York iron fire alarm bell tower
    - 450 West 33rd Street (Box 25, Folder 480)
      N.Y. Daily News Building
    - West 38th Street (Box 25, Folder 481)
      residence of E.K. Rossiter
    - 113 -- 115 East 40th Street (Box 25, Folder 482)
      A.I.A. Office Building
    - East 42nd Street at Park Avenue (Box 25, Folder 483)
      Grand Central Station
    - 60 East 42nd Street (Box 25, Folder 484)
    - 220 East 42nd Street (Box 25, Folder 485)
      News Building
    - 122 West 42nd Street (Box 25, Folder 486)
      Chanin Building
    - 330 West 42nd Street (Box 25, Folder 487)
      McGraw-Hill Building
    - 56 West 45th Street (Box 25, Folder 488)
    - between 51st and 52nd Streets (Box 25, Folder 489)
    - 15 West 51st Street (Box 25, Folder 490)
      Esso Building
    - 51 West 52nd Street (Box 25, Folder 491)
      CBS Building
    - 53rd Street (Box 25, Folder 492)
      Youle's Shot Tower
    - 9 -- 11 West 54th Street (Box 25, Folder 493)
      U.S. Trust Building
    - 2 East 55th Street (Box 25, Folder 494)
      St. Regis Hotel
    - 2 West 55th Street (Box 25, Folder 495)
      Hotel Gorham
    - 241 West 57th Street (Box 25, Folder 496)
      General Motors Building
    - 250 West 57th Street (Box 25, Folder 497)
      Fisk Rubber Co. Building
    - West 58th to West 59th Street, and Grand Army Plaza (Box 25, Folder 498)
      Plaza Apartment House
    - 61st Street and Fifth Avenue (Box 26, Folder 499)
      residence of E.T. Gerry
    - 81 -- 85 East 125th Street (Box 26, Folder 500)
      Mount Morris Bank Building
    - 11 --15 West 88th Street (Box 26, Folder 501)
      The Progress Club
    - 132 -- 140 West 125th Street (Box 26, Folder 502)
      H. C. F. Koch and Co. Building
    - Manhattan buildings- "A" -- "C" (Box 26, Folder 503)
      includes American Art-Union League, Anderson Building, Bolkenhayn
    - Manhattan buildings -- "D" -- "Z" (Box 26, Folder 504)
      includes Graphic Arts Building, Hartford Building, Indemnity Building, Larkin Building
    - unidentified Manhattan buildings (Box 26, Folder 505)
    - unidentified Manhattan buildings (Box 26, Folder 506)
    - unidentified Manhattan buildings (Box 26, Folder 507)
    - unidentified Manhattan buildings (Box 26, Folder 508)
    - unidentified Soho buildings (Box 26, Folder 509)
    - New York City bridges (Box 27, Folder 510)
    - Lower Manhattan panoramic views (Box 27, Folder 511)
    - Lower Manhattan maps (Box 27, Folder 512)
    - Lower Manhattan maps (Box 27, Folder 513)
    - Soho maps (Box 27, Folder 514)
    - Soho maps (Box 27, Folder 515)
    - miscellaneous architectural plans of S.A. Warner (unidentified Soho building) (Box 27, Folder 516)
    - elevator reproductions (Box 27, Folder 517)
      includes print copy of electric elevator in Demarest Building on Fifth Avenue
  - ARCHITECTS
    This subseries is mounted copy prints of portraits of architect, arranged by sitter.
    - portraits of architects (Box 27, Folder 518)
      includes Burnham and Root, John M. Van Osdel, A.I.A. Convention, George Post
  - UNITED STATES (by State)
    This subseries is mounted copy prints of buildings in the United States arranged alphabetically by state and thereunder by city. Within a city the buildings are arranged alphabetically by building name; prominent ones are mentioned in the finding aid. Note that Brooklyn, New York, is included in this subseries and not in the first subseries, which is exclusively Manhattan buildings as originally arranged in Dr. Weisman's work.
    - Alabama
      - Birmingham (Box 28, Folder 519)
        T.F. Wright Dry Goods
    - California
      - Los Angeles (Box 28, Folder 520)
        includes UCLA Medical Center, Hillcrest Country Club, Police Facilities Building
      - San Francisco (Box 28, Folder 521)
        includes Crown Zellerback, Wells and Fargo Express Company, Spreckles Building
    - Colorado
      - Boulder (Box 28, Folder 522)
        National Center for Atmospheric Research
      - Denver (Box 28, Folder 523)
        Boston Building, Equitable Life Insurance Building
    - Connecticut
      - Hartford (Box 28, Folder 524)
        Connecticut Life Insurance Co. Building, Cheney's Block
      - New Canaan (Box 28, Folder 525)
        Wiley House
    - District of Columbia (Box 28, Folder 526)
      includes Dulles Airport, Columbian University, Marriot's Motor Inn, Dayton House
    - Florida
      - Miami (Box 28, Folder 527)
        includes Americana Hotel
    - Illinois
      - Chicago--"A" Buildings (Box 28, Folder 528)
        includes Auditorium Building, Academy of Music, Adams Express Co.
      - Chicago--"B" Buildings (Box 28, Folder 529 - 530)
        includes Borden Block, Ballard Block, Banker's Building, Bell Building
      - Chicago--"C" Buildings (Box 29, Folder 531)
        includes Chamber of Commerce, Chicago and Northwest Passenger Station
      - Chicago--"D" Buildings (Box 29, Folder 532)
        includes Daily News Building, Davis Store, Dearborn State Bank, Dearborn Theater
      - Chicago--"E" Buildings (Box 29, Folder 533)
        Edison Building, Equitable Tower
      - Chicago--"F" Buildings (Box 29, Folder 534)
        includes Fair Building, Federal Center, First National Bank, Fisher Building
      - Chicago--"G" Buildings (Box 29, Folder 536)
        Great Northern Hotel and Annex, Gaff Office Building, Greenbaum Building
      - Chicago--"H" Buildings (Box 29, Folder 537)
        includes Harris Trust Co., Home Life Insurance Co., Honore Block
      - Chicago--"I" Buildings (Box 30, Folder 30)
        Insurance Exchange Office Building, Illinois Merchants Bank Building, Inland Steel
      - Chicago--"J" Buildings (Box 30, Folder 539)
        J.B. Mallers Office Building, John Hancock Mutual Life Insurance Co. Building
      - Chicago--"K" Buildings (Box 30, Folder 540)
        Kendall Block, Knisely Building
      - Chicago--"L" Buildings (Box 30, Folder 541)
        includes Leiter Buildings, London Guarantee Building, Lake Michigan Building
      - Chicago--"M" Buildings (Box 30, Folder 542 - 544)
        includes Major Block, Masonic Temple, McCormick Buildings, Monadnock Block
      - Chicago--"N" Buildings (Box 30, Folder 545)
        New York Life Insurance Building, Nixon Building, North American Building
      - Chicago--"O" Buildings (Box 31, Folder 546)
        includes Opera House, Otis Block, Owings Building, Old Colony Building
      - Chicago--"P-Q" Buildings (Box 31, Folder 547)
        includes Palmer House, Palmolive Building, Phoenix Building, Portland Block
      - Chicago--"R" Buildings (Box 31, Folder 548)
        includes Reaper Block, Rookery, T.P. Randall Store, Reynold's Block, Rialto Office
      - Chicago--"S" Buildings (Box 31, Folder 549-550)
        includes Schiller Building, Selz, Schwab Factory, Smyth Building, Standard Club
      - Chicago--"T" Buildings (Box 31, Folder 551)
        includes Tacoma Building, Telephone Building, Tremont House, Tribune Building
      - Chicago--"U" Buildings (Box 32, Folder 32)
        Union Building, Unity Building
      - Chicago--"V" Buildings (Box 32, Folder 553)
        Venetian Office Building
      - Chicago--"W" Buildings (Box 32, Folder 554)
        includes Walker Warehouse, Women's Temple, Wrigley Building, Wells Building
      - Chicago--"X-Z" Buildings (Box 32, Folder 555)
        Z. M. Hall Store
      - Chicago-- miscellaneous plans (Box 32, Folder 556)
        includes first plan of Chicago, Lake Meadows Redevelopment Project
      - Chicago-- Jebne and Almini street views (Box 32, Folder 557)
      - Chicago-- Rand, McNally street views (Box 32, Folder 558-559)
      - Chicago-- miscellaneous street views (Box 32, Folder 560)
    - Indiana
      - Fort Wayne (Box 33, Folder 561)
        McDonald and Taylor Building, Old National Bank
      - Hammond (Box 33, Folder 562)
        Standard Oil Co. Building
      - Indianapolis (Box 33, Folder 563)
    - Iowa
      - Des Moines (Box 33, Folder 564)
        Allen residence
      - Mason City (Box 33, Folder 565)
        Blythe House
    - Louisiana
      - Baton Rouge (Box 33, Folder 566)
        Esso Office Building
      - New Orleans (Box 33, Folder 567)
        Cotton Exchange
    - Maine
      - York Harbor (Box 33, Folder 568)
        Redcote
    - Maryland
      - Baltimore - "A" -- "F" Buildings (Box 33, Folder 569)
        includes B. and O. Building, Farmers and Merchants Bank, Fidelity Building
      - Baltimore - "H" -- "M" Buildings (Box 33, Folder 570)
        includes Massachusetts Building, McArburg Brothers tobacco warehouse
      - Baltimore - "P" -- "W" Buildings (Box 33, Folder 571)
        Rennert House, Sun Building, Robins Paper Company, Rombon Building
    - Massachusetts
      - Beverly (Box 33, Folder 572)
        United Shoe Machinery Co.
      - Boston - "A" Buildings (Box 34, Folder 573)
        includes Ames Buildings, Auchmuty Building, Adams Building, Ames Building
      - Boston - "B" -- "C" Buildings (Box 34, Folder 574)
        includes Boston Real Estate Trust, Brazer's Building, Chamber of Commerce
      - Boston - "E" -- "J" Buildings (Box 34, Folder 575)
        includes Exchange Building, International Trust Building, Eben D. Jordan Building
      - Boston - "M" -- "Z" Buildings (Box 34, Folder 576)
        includes R. H. White and Co. Building, Shreve, Crump and Low Store
      - Boston - miscellaneous buildings (Box 34, Folder 577)
      - Fitchburg (Box 35, Folder 578)
        Y.M.C.A.
      - Lexington (Box 35, Folder 579)
        small house for Five Fields Community Project
      - Lowell (Box 35, Folder 580)
        Hildreth Building
      - Manchester-By-The-Sea (Box 35, Folder 581)
        Kragside, G. Nixon Black's summer house
      - Uxbridge (Box 35, Folder 582)
        Town Hall
      - Worcester (Box 35, Folder 583)
        State Mutual Life Insurance Co. Building
    - Michigan
      - Detroit (Box 35, Folder 584)
        includes Hammond Building, The Majestic, Book Tower, Eaton Tower
    - Minnesota
      - Duluth (Box 34, Folder 585)
        George Spencer and Co. Building
      - Minneapolis (Box 34, Folder 586)
        includes Foshay Tower, National Bank of Commerce, N.Y. Life Insurance Co.
      - St. Paul--"A" -- "G" Buildings (Box 34, Folder 587)
        includes E.D. Chamberlin's Building, Germania Buildings
      - St. Paul--"L" -- "N" Buildings (Box 34, Folder 588)
        includes National German American Bank, N. Y. Life Insurance Co.
      - St. Paul--"P" -- "Z" Buildings (Box 34, Folder 589)
        Pioneer Press Building, Ryan Hotel, Phoenix Building, Ramsey County Court House
    - Missouri
      - Kansas City (Box 36, Folder 36)
        includes American Bank Building, Board of Trade, Midland Hotel
      - St. Louis--"A" -- "G" Buildings (Box 36, Folder 591)
        includes Bell Telephone Co., Fullerton-Terry Building, Globe Democrat Printing
      - St. Louis--"H" -- "R" Buildings (Box 36, Folder 592)
        includes Laclede Building, Martin Building, Phipps and Wallace store
      - St. Louis--"S" -- "W" Buildings (Box 36, Folder 593)
        Security Building, Union Trust Building, Wainwright Building
    - Nebraska
      - Omaha (Box 37, Folder 594)
        Bee Building
    - New Jersey
      - Bernardsville (Box 37, Folder 595)
        George B. Post house
      - Hoboken (Box 37, Folder 596)
        Hoboken Land and Improvement Co.
      - Jersey City (Box 37, Folder 597)
        J.F. Ward House
      - Montclair (Box 37, Folder 598)
      - Newark (Box 37, Folder 599)
        Prudential Life Insurance Co. Building
    - New York
      - Albany (Box 37, Folder 600)
        includes New York State Capital interiors, R.C. Pruyn House
      - Brooklyn (Box 37, Folder 601)
        includes Brooklyn Eagle Building, City Hall, First Reformed Church
      - Buffalo (Box 37, Folder 602)
        includes Erie County Savings Bank, Guaranty Building
      - Elmira (Box 37, Folder 603)
        Y.M.C.A. and Steele Memorial Library
      - Kings County, Long Island (Box 37, Folder 604)
        Arlington House
      - Rochester (Box 37, Folder 605)
        Elwood Memorial Building
      - Roosevelt (Box 37, Folder 606)
        Roosevelt Shopping Center
      - Troy (Box 37, Folder 607)
        Troy Savings Bank Music Hall
      - Yorktown Heights (Box 37, Folder 608)
        IBM Research Center
    - North Carolina
      - Asheville (Box 37, Folder 610)
        G.W. Vanderbilt's Biltmore House
    - Ohio
      - Canton (Box 37, Folder 609)
        Central Savings Bank
      - Cincinnati (Box 37, Folder 611)
        includes Chamber of Commerce, First National Bank, Shillito Warehouse, City Hall
      - Cleveland (Box 37, Folder 612)
        includes Chamber of Commerce, Cleveland Arcade, Cleveland Trust Co.
      - Columbus (Box 37, Folder 613)
        American Insurance Union Citadel
    - Oklahoma
      - Bartlesville (Box 38, Folder 614)
        Price Tower
      - Tulsa (Box 38, Folder 615)
        First National Bank Building
    - Oregon
      - Portland (Box 38, Folder 616)
        Chamber of Commerce, United Bank Building
    - Pennsylvania
      - Erie (Box 38, Folder 617)
        building for J.F. Downing
      - Lewisburg (Box 38, Folder 618)
        Bucknell University
      - Philadelphia--"A" Buildings (Box 38, Folder 619)
        includes Arcade, Ashmead Printing House, Athenaeum
      - Philadelphia--"B" Buildings (Box 38, Folder 620-621)
        includes Bailey Store, Bank of Commerce, Bank of North America
      - Philadelphia--"C" Buildings (Box 38, Folder 622-623)
        includes Caleb Cope Store, Cornelius and Baker Factory, Corn Exchange Bank
      - Philadelphia--"D" Buildings (Box 38, Folder 624)
        Darlington, Runk and Co. Building, Delaware Mutual Insurance Building
      - Philadelphia--"E" Buildings (Box 38, Folder 625)
        Elliot and Dunn Bank, Ellis Building, English Commissioners' Building
      - Philadelphia--"F" Buildings (Box 39, Folder 626)
        Fidelity Building, First National Bank, Finn and Burton's Warehouse
      - Philadelphia--"G" Buildings (Box 39, Folder 627)
        Girard Buildings, Goldsmith's Hall, Granite Block, Guarantee Trust Building
      - Philadelphia--"H" Buildings (Box 39, Folder 628)
        includes Harrison Building, Hauel Store, Horstmann Factory
      - Philadelphia--"I" Buildings (Box 39, Folder 629)
        includes Insurance Company of State of Pennsylvania, Independence National Bank
      - Philadelphia--"J" Buildings (Box 39, Folder 630)
        includes Jackson Building, Japanese Exhibit Buildings, Jayne Building, J.C. Lucas
      - Philadelphia--"K" Buildings (Box 39, Folder 631)
        Keim Store
      - Philadelphia--"L" Buildings (Box 39, Folder 632)
        includes Leland Building; Liverpool, London and Globe Insurance Co. Building
      - Philadelphia--"M" Buildings (Box 40, Folder 40)
        includes Manhattan Life Insurance Co., Masonic Temple, Megargee Warehouse
      - Philadelphia--"N" Buildings (Box 40, Folder 634)
        National Bank of the Republic, Natt Store, Newton's Confectionary
      - Philadelphia--"O" Buildings (Box 40, Folder 635)
        Oakford Hat Store, Odd Fellows Hall, Orne's Store
      - "P" Buildings (Box 40, Folder 636)
        includes Penn Mutual Building, Philadelphia Bank, Phoenix Block
      - Philadelphia--"P" Buildings (Box 40, Folder 637)
      - "P" Buildings (Box 40, Folder 638)
      - Philadelphia--"R" Buildings (Box 40, Folder 639)
        includes Drug Store, Real Estate Title and Trust Co., Ridgeway's Drug Store
      - Philadelphia--"S" Buildings (Box 40, Folder 640)
        includes Schuylkill Navy Club, Sharpless Buildings, Swain's Block, Singerly Building
      - Philadelphia--"T" Buildings (Box 41, Folder 641)
        includes Telegraph Building, Thomas White Store, Times Building, Tower Building
      - Philadelphia--"U" Buildings (Box 41, Folder 642)
        United Firemen's Insurance Co., United States Hotel
      - Philadelphia--"V" Building (Box 41, Folder 643)
        Van Dyke Building
      - Philadelphia--"W" Buildings (Box 41, Folder 644)
        includes Wright, Hunter Building, Wanamaker's Department Store, Wattson Bakery
      - Philadelphia--"Y-Z" Buildings (Box 41, Folder 645)
        Y.M.C.A. Building
      - Philadelphia-- Rae's Views, Chestnut Street, 1851 (Box 41, Folder 646-647)
      - Philadelphia-- Baxter's Views, predominantly Chestnut Street, 1856 (Box 41, Folder 648)
      - Philadelphia-- miscellaneous Chestnut Street buildings (Box 42, Folder 649)
      - Philadelphia-- miscellaneous buildings and street views (Box 42, Folder 650)
      - Pittsburgh--"A" -- "H" Buildings (Box 42, Folder 651)
        includes Alcoa Building, Heinz Plant, Arbuckle Warehouse, Bank of Pittsburgh
      - Pittsburgh--"J" -- "Z" Buildings (Box 42, Folder 652)
        includes J.J. Vandergrift Building, Masonic Building, Park Building, Union Exchange
      - Pittsburgh-- miscellaneous buildings and city views (Box 42, Folder 653)
    - Rhode Island
      - Providence (Box 42, Folder 654)
        includes Granite Block, Roger Williams Bank, Arcade, Cheapside
    - South Carolina
      - Charleston (Box 43, Folder 655)
        Commercial Exchange, First National Bank
    - Tennessee
      - Nashville (Box 43, Folder 656)
        bank and office building for Wm. M. Duncan
    - Texas
      - Austin (Box 43, Folder 657)
        American National Bank
      - Houston (Box 43, Folder 658)
        M & M Building
    - Utah
      - Salt Lake City (Box 43, Folder 659)
        Deseret National Bank
    - Washington
      - Seattle (Box 43, Folder 660)
        Norton Building, Seattle National Bank Building
      - Tacoma (Box 43, Folder 661)
        Chamber of Commerce
    - Wisconsin
      - Madison (Box 43, Folder 662)
        City-County Building, Forest Products Laboratory
      - Milwaukee (Box 43, Folder 663)
        A.O. Smith Building, Pabst Office Building
  - INTERNATIONAL CITIES(by country)
    This subseries is mounted copy prints of buildings in countries other than United States. These are arranged alphabetically by country and thereunder by city.
    - Austria
      - Vienna (Box 44, Folder 664)
        Germania Building
    - Belgium
      - Antwerp (Box 44, Folder 665)
        Tower of the Old Bourse
      - Ypres (Box 44, Folder 666)
        Cloth Hall
    - Canada
      - Montreal (Box 44, Folder 667)
        Montreal Board of Trade, New York Life Insurance Co. Building
      - Toronto (Box 44, Folder 668)
        Federal Centre
    - Dominican Republic
      - Santo Domingo (Box 44, Folder 669)
        lighthouse
    - France
      - Paris (Box 44, Folder 670)
        includes Pavillon de la Bibliotheque du Louvre, Chamber of Commerce
    - Germany
      - Aachen (Box 44, Folder 671)
      - Berlin (Box 44, Folder 672)
        Anhalt Railway Station, Imperial Bank, Town Hall
      - Hildesheim (Box 44, Folder 673)
        Butchers Guild Hall
    - Greece
      - Athens (Box 44, Folder 674)
        stoa of Attalos
    - Italy
      - Ancona (Box 44, Folder 675)
        Cathedral
      - Assisi (Box 44, Folder 676)
        Church of St. Francis of Assisi
      - Brescia (Box 44, Folder 677)
        Palazzo Communale
      - Ferrara (Box 44, Folder 678)
      - Florence (Box 44, Folder 679)
        Or San Michele
      - Ostia (Box 44, Folder 680)
        Ostia Exchange, Theatre and Piazzale Delle Corpozione
      - Pescia (Box 44, Folder 681)
        Flower Market
      - Pistoia (Box 44, Folder 682)
        Plaza of the Cathedral
      - Udine (Box 44, Folder 683)
        Palazzo Publico
      - Miscellaneous buildings (Box 44, Folder 684-687)
      - Miscellaneous buildings (cont.) (Box 45, Folder 688 - 697)
      - Miscellaneous buildings (cont.) (Box 46, Folder 698)
    - Japan
      - Tokyo (Box 46, Folder 699)
        Imperial Hotel
    - Mexico
      - Mexico City (Box 46, Folder 700)
    - Netherlands
      - Amsterdam (Box 46, Folder 701)
        Old Stock Exchange of Amsterdam
    - Spain
      - Saragossa (Box 46, Folder 702)
        La Lonja (Exchange)
      - Valencia (Box 46, Folder 703)
    - United Kingdom-England
      - Bristol (Box 46, Folder 704)
        Bristol Merchant Exchange
      - Kensington (Box 46, Folder 705)
        Lowther Lodge
      - Leicester (Box 46, Folder 706)
        Alliance Assurance Co. Building
      - London--"A" -- "E" Buildings (Box 46, Folder 707)
        includes Alliance Assurance Building, Burlington Arcade, Charing Cross, City Bank
      - London--"F" -- "Z" Buildings (Box 46, Folder 708)
        includes Festival of Britain, Regents Canal, Grovesnor Square, Lloyd's Bank
      - Manchester (Box 46, Folder 709)
        warehouses for Brown, Son and Co.
      - Newcastle (Box 46, Folder 710)
        Royal Arcade
      - Nottinghamshire (Box 46, Folder 711)
        Wollaton Hall
      - Sussex (Box 46, Folder 712)
        Leyes Wood
    - United Kingdom--Wales
      - Abergele (Box 46, Folder 713)
        Kinmel Park
      - Brynmaur (Box 46, Folder 714)
        escape stairway at rubber factory
- Series II. Negatives
  Series II consists of 3,800 film negatives, measuring 4 x 5 inches. They contain much the same images as the mounted copy prints, with only a few exceptions, notably Rockefeller Center images, used by Dr. Weisman for his dissertation and subsequent lectures and articles on the genesis of Rockefeller Center. These images include those of Rockefeller Center original designs and models when it was to be Metropolitan Square, housing three tall office buildings and a new Metropolitan Opera House around a plaza. The fall of the stock market ended these particular plans after the Opera could no longer afford to move.
  Series II is arranged according to Weisman's own arrangement and reflects his particular interest in the area. This series is divided into five subseries: Soho, Manhattan, George P. Post, United States, and International.
  - SOHO
    This subseries is negatives of copy prints of Soho arranged alphabetically by street address. Included here are only those streets that Weisman considered part of Soho for his project and that subsequently became the Soho Cast-Iron Historic District. The boundaries for this district are West Houston Street in the north, West Broadway in the west, Crosby Street in the east and Canal Street in the south. Broadway appears in both subseries one and two but there is no overlap of addresses. This first subseries ends with miscellaneous Soho buildings and maps of Soho.
    - 423 -- 600 Broadway 429 --500 Broome Street 305 -- 375 Canal Street 60 -- 131 Grand Street (Box 47)
    - 14 -- 148 Greene Street 27 -- 50 Howard Street 7 -- 169 Mercer Street (Box 48)
    - 88 -- 143 Prince Street 79 -- 157 Spring Street 307 -- 465 West Broadway 12 -- 155 Wooster Street maps miscellaneous building plans (Box 49)
  - MANHATTAN